This file is a merged representation of a subset of the codebase, containing specifically included files, combined into a single document by Repomix.

<file_summary>
This section contains a summary of this file.

<purpose>
This file contains a packed representation of a subset of the repository's contents that is considered the most important context.
It is designed to be easily consumable by AI systems for analysis, code review,
or other automated processes.
</purpose>

<file_format>
The content is organized as follows:
1. This summary section
2. Repository information
3. Directory structure
4. Repository files (if enabled)
5. Multiple file entries, each consisting of:
  - File path as an attribute
  - Full contents of the file
</file_format>

<usage_guidelines>
- This file should be treated as read-only. Any changes should be made to the
  original repository files, not this packed version.
- When processing this file, use the file path to distinguish
  between different files in the repository.
- Be aware that this file may contain sensitive information. Handle it with
  the same level of security as you would the original repository.
</usage_guidelines>

<notes>
- Some files may have been excluded based on .gitignore rules and Repomix's configuration
- Binary files are not included in this packed representation. Please refer to the Repository Structure section for a complete list of file paths, including binary files
- Only files matching these patterns are included: **/*.go
- Files matching patterns in .gitignore are excluded
- Files matching default ignore patterns are excluded
- Files are sorted by Git change count (files with more changes are at the bottom)
</notes>

</file_summary>

<directory_structure>
cmd/
  demo.go
  root.go
main.go
</directory_structure>

<files>
This section contains the contents of the repository's files.

<file path="cmd/demo.go">
/*
Copyright © 2026 NAME HERE <EMAIL ADDRESS>

*/
package cmd

import (
	"fmt"

	"github.com/spf13/cobra"
)

// demoCmd represents the demo command
var demoCmd = &cobra.Command{
	Use:   "demo",
	Short: "A brief description of your command",
	Long: `A longer description that spans multiple lines and likely contains examples
and usage of using your command. For example:

Cobra is a CLI library for Go that empowers applications.
This application is a tool to generate the needed files
to quickly create a Cobra application.`,
	Run: func(cmd *cobra.Command, args []string) {
		fmt.Println("demo called")
	},
}

func init() {
	rootCmd.AddCommand(demoCmd)

	// Here you will define your flags and configuration settings.

	// Cobra supports Persistent Flags which will work for this command
	// and all subcommands, e.g.:
	// demoCmd.PersistentFlags().String("foo", "", "A help for foo")

	// Cobra supports local flags which will only run when this command
	// is called directly, e.g.:
	// demoCmd.Flags().BoolP("toggle", "t", false, "Help message for toggle")
}
</file>

<file path="cmd/root.go">
/*
Created © 2026 Limp Cheney limpdev@proton.me
*/
package cmd

import (
	"os"

	"github.com/spf13/cobra"
)

// rootCmd represents the base command when called without any subcommands
var rootCmd = &cobra.Command{
	Use:   "makecell",
	Short: "Excel template generator",
	Long:  `Excel template generator...`,
	// Uncomment the following line if your bare application
	// has an action associated with it:
	// Run: func(cmd *cobra.Command, args []string) { },
}

// Execute adds all child commands to the root command and sets flags appropriately.
// This is called by main.main(). It only needs to happen once to the rootCmd.
func Execute() {
	err := rootCmd.Execute()
	if err != nil {
		os.Exit(1)
	}
}

func init() {
	// Here you will define your flags and configuration settings.
	// Cobra supports persistent flags, which, if defined here,
	// will be global for your application.

	// rootCmd.PersistentFlags().StringVar(&cfgFile, "config", "", "config file (default is $HOME/.makecell.yaml)")

	// Cobra also supports local flags, which will only run
	// when this action is called directly.
	rootCmd.Flags().BoolP("toggle", "t", false, "Help message for toggle")
}
</file>

<file path="main.go">
/*
Created © 2026 Limp Cheney limpdev@proton.me
*/
package main

import "makecell/cmd"

func main() {
	cmd.Execute()
}
</file>

</files>
